# MELKORKA BJARNADÓTTIR

CPR-number: 230902-7356



## **About Me**

I. am 21 years old from Iceland. I am very interested in marketing and design and plan to study something related to that field. I lived in Denmark when I was young and then decided to move back after going to Vejle Idræthøjskole for six months. I am very ambitious, hard-working and always on time!



+354 7898985



melkorkabjarnad@gmail.com



Jernbane Allé 18, 2720 Vanløse

#### LANGUAGES

- English very good
- Danish good
- Icelandic very good

#### **INTERESTS**

- Sports
- Outdoor activities
- Marketing
- Design
- Spending time with family and friends

#### RECOMMENDATIONS

#### Dagný Jónsdóttir

Department manager, Hrafnista Phone number: +354 6939575 Email: Dagny.jonsdottir@hrafnista.is

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Sales Assistant JD Sports

2023 - now

I have been working as a sales assistant in JD since October 2023

### Caregiver

**Hrafnista Nursing Home** 

2020 - 2024

I worked at Hrafnista since March 2020. I mainly worked with people with dementia, Parkinson's and Alzheimer's. I learned first aid at work and various other skills that will benefit me in life. I enjoy helping people and have therefore enjoyed my job at Hrafnista over the past few years.

Waitress Saffran restaurant 2019-2020

I worked as a waitress at Saffran for 9 months.

Gardening Landspitalinn 2019

I worked as a gardener one summer at the hospital.

Service worker Subway 2018-2019

I worked as a service worker at Subway

Coach

Soccer summer school 2017-2018

I worked as a soccer coach for childrren for 2 summers.

### **EDUCATION**

University , 2024 - now KEA - Multimediadesign

High School Diploma, 2018 - 2021

Flensborg - Natural Science

Sports School, 2022

Vejle Idræthøjskole